(music) (bus stopping)
(music)
(Music playing)(Mans voice in the backround)
A day on the Bus
Lonely is a Bus
(Music playing)(Mans voice in the background)
(Traffic noise)
Hey John, I'm sorry, sorry about the other night. I just got this
This thing with Kate and just didn't want to be around a group of strangers
hey c'mon forget about it, hey forget about it, forget about it, forget about it
So how is this thing
-How's the show?
-Well, I thought I gave a command performance.
-Good
-Opinions varied. So who's to say, I don't know, who's to say what really
What really happened? Um I'm trying to stay positive with it.
Are these supposed to be up here?
Uh, those are not supposed to be up here actually. People just leave
leave things here, a bunch of savages. So what happened between you and Kate? It was just another argument about
I don't even know. Its just, we just started yelling at each other.
Just spontaneous yelling. Just one minute you're fine, and the next minute ah! Ah! AH! AH!
Just zero to sixty.
sixty.
That sounds terrible. Is that what, is, that what marriage is like?
That's what my marriage is like.
Jesus! It sounds like a nightmare.
We haven't even talked to each other since then.
What does that mean?
No words have gone from my mouth to her ears.
And vice versa.
Thank you.
That's crazy. You know you guys are adults
It's in a committed relationship right? What happens if you have to pass each other in the hallway? Just nothing, just dead eyes the whole time. Just ships in the night? You guys just
I just schwooh. just...
Oh yeah we don't make eye contact.
OOoh
Takes care of that.
Ooh well that's smart
I mean in my experience if you ignore a problem long enough
just long enough. It actually just goes away.
(laughs) sure, just look at Hitler.
Not sure I'm following...
Well, he
He had a problem. With a certain group of people.
Oooh
Not gonna say who.
Sure.
The jews!
And, uh, instead of ignoring his problems, like we all should! He started a war, and uh, then we got in on it. And bleh bleh bleh Fat man, little boy!
Boy, god. It did not end well for him. Suffice to say, dude just ignore your problems. And I think that's a lesson for all of us.
Wait, so you're saying I shouldn't engage in mass ethnic cleansing?
cleansing in the hopes of making my marriage better?
Dude! I'm just saying you gotta explore all the diplomatic options first! If that fails I don't know what to tell you.
That's probably good advice.
(alarm clock)
(cellphone alarm)
(sounds of traffic)
Hey! You were on the 9:05 yesterday morning right?
Yeah
You know, this was the third time that that bus was gone
has gotten me to work late in the last week. I mean I know that it is not an exact science, but, I just feel like if you're gonna say the bus is going to be there at 9:30, it should be there
there around 9:30 you know. Not 9:50.
Yeah, I think that bus driver's still new.
Unfortunately, still new bus driver isn't really a
really a very good excuse for my boss. Well, he's the kind of person that thinks if you're not five minutes early then you're late.
Sorry.
It's OK.
I mean, he can't really afford to fire me. I mean, where else is he going to find a temporary office assistant who's willing to work for minimum wage and no benefits.
What about your boss? Does he, uh, does he get mad if you get to work late?
I don't really  have a boss. I mean, technically I do. But I can't see him getting too worked up about
about time cards.
Where do you work?
Brave new books. Its an alternative book store. You know, everything you know about 9/11 being an inside
-Job, the reptilian elite, we've got it all.
-Sound's like it. So, why do you take the bus? I mean, there are only like
Not Everyone fits in a Box